[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Israels major airport is located near Eilat.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The dewberry is closely related to this other berry fruit.", "correct_answer": "Blackberry", "incorrect_answers": ["Grape", "Strawberry", "Wolfberry"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 2002 movie 28 Days Later was filmed entirley in Scotland.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these medical conditions is linked to excessive salt consumption?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Duodenal ulcers and gastric ulcers", "Edema", "Osteoporosis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following types of music are not generally associated with Jamaica?", "correct_answer": "Calypso", "incorrect_answers": ["Mento", "Reggae", "Ska"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The movie Trois couleurs: Rouge (Three Colors: Red) is about a girl who discovers her neighbour is keen on invading peoples privacy. This is her profession.", "correct_answer": "Model", "incorrect_answers": ["Photographer", "Teacher", "Actress"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1963 this soundtrack broke the record for the most weeks as the number one album on the Billboard charts.", "correct_answer": "West Side Story", "incorrect_answers": ["The Body Guard", "Saturday Night Fever", "South Pacific"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the meaning of the word Sarcophilus, the name of the genus that the Tasmanian devil belongs to?", "correct_answer": "Meat-lover", "incorrect_answers": ["Devil creature", "Blood-lover", "Dog-like"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the comedy film Office Space, what was the name of the favorite show that Peter and Joanna enjoyed watching together while they were dating?", "correct_answer": "Kung Fu", "incorrect_answers": ["The Incredible Hulk", "The A-Team", "Happy Days"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In The Office, what alias does Michael Scott often use?", "correct_answer": "Michael Scarn", "incorrect_answers": ["Art Van der Lay", "David Wallace", "Sara Tesasdale"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first oil refinery in the world, bombarded in 1943 by US Air Force in operation Tidal Wave, was built in this country in 1856.", "correct_answer": "Romania", "incorrect_answers": ["Germany", "Iran", "Italy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A chimp named Laika was the first living mammal to orbit the earth.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]